# MRUNAL KUMAVAT

## **UX/UI** Designer | Researcher

## LinkedIn

mrunnuk@gmail.com

+1 650(789)-4958

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://mrunalkumavat.online/

## **SKILLS**

UX Research & Strategy

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Interface Design

Logo Design & Branding

Responsive Design

**Usability Testing** 

Diagramming

HTML | CSS

## **TOOLS**

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Miro

Figjam

Dovetail

VS Code

Github

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Google UX Design Professional

Issued Feb 2022 🐧 See credential

UI/UX Design Training by Internshala

Issued April 2021 🕄 See credential

Visual Elements of User Interface Design Issued July 2022 § See credential

## SUMMARY

A Full Stack UX Researcher & Designer, with the ability to blend technical proficiency with artistic flair to forge engaging and functional user experiences.

Possesses a comprehensive skill set, encompassing in-depth user research, vibrant visual design, and strategic product management, dedicated to delivering innovative UX/UI design solutions that elevate user satisfaction and drive business success.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **UX/UI Designer** Weedor

Feb 2023 - Present

- Research Phase: Weedor, Inc. empowers African schools to create inclusive, innovative learning environments, quality education for all.
  My research involved analyzing the user interface, user experience, and overall functionality of their current website.
- **Branding Elements**: Creating consistent and cohesive branding elements, including logos, color palettes, and visual assets.
- Website Redesign: Redesigning the company's website to improve userfriendliness, visual appeal, and alignment with the latest design trends.

### **UI Designer** Initialyze

May 2022 - Aug 2022

- Website Product Page Design: I provided design ideas for the website's product page, offering multiple solutions and innovative ideas to enhance its design.
- Social Media Brochures: I also designed brochures for social media, ensuring they were engaging, on-brand, and effectively communicated the company's message.

### **Graphics Designer** Learnovate Ecommerce

July 2021 - Oct 2021

 Layouts and Production Designs: I designed layouts and production designs for various applications, including advertisements, brochures, magazines, ID cards, and reports.

### **EDUCATION**

MICA, Maryland Institute of Arts, USA Master Of professional Studies in UX Design

College of Engineering, Pune, India B.Tech in Computer Engineering